<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Binance Square News</title>
    <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square</link>
    <description>Latest news from Binance Square with full content</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Binance Square RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: ‘Not the First, Won’t Be the Last’ — AMA Today on FUD</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-not-the-first-won-t-be-the-last-ama-today-on-fud-35762544054497</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/image/pgc/202601/tdvGNabCqDHdStwB1cY6uG.jpeg" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), Binance founder and former CEO, posted on X stating that this is not the first time—and won’t be the last—that he has faced FUD attacks. He noted that tonight’s AMA will take a de&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf4fc60031baaee10b46286e89c43482</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that something significant is on the horizon for users of Binance Wallet Earn. The platform has hinted at an upcoming development, urging users to stay engaged and attentive to future updates. While specific details remain undisclosed, the announcement suggests that Binance Wallet Earn may soon introduce new features or opportunities for its users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The message, marked by a sense of anticipation, encourages users to remain connected with Binance Wallet Earn to ensure they are among the first to learn about the forthcoming changes. This announcement aligns with Binance's ongoing efforts to enhance its services and provide users with innovative ways to manage and grow their digital assets. As the platform continues to evolve, users are advised to keep an eye on official channels for further information regarding this anticipated development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Reports 2025 Achievements and Plans to Convert $100 Million SAFU Fund to Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-binance-reports-2025-achievements-and-plans-to-convert-100-million-safu-fund-to-bitcoin-35775514215994</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance published an open letter to the crypto community on Binance Blog, and announced that market volatility and pressures have impacted the company alongside the broader industry, reflecting the in&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ddb0e76798a3d3ca78d4f6ed3320423</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that users of Binance Wallet who possess 240 or more Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the upcoming Pre-TGE Prime Sale event for Espresso. This event can be accessed through the Alpha event page, and participation will require the deduction of 15 Alpha Points.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Espresso Prime Sale offers a refund option, ensuring that users who do not claim their tokens within the designated period will have their staked BNB and Alpha Points automatically refunded. The claim period for this Prime Sale is set for 24 hours, concluding at 14:00 UTC on February 11, 2026. It is crucial for participants to make their claims within this timeframe, as any claims made after the deadline will not be accepted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;For those who miss the claim deadline, Binance assures that their staked BNB and Alpha Points will be returned to their participating wallet within seven business days. This structured approach aims to facilitate a smooth and efficient process for all participants, ensuring that users have the opportunity to engage in the Prime Sale while also providing a safety net for those unable to claim in time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Binance's Unique Work Culture and Core Values</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-understanding-binance-s-unique-work-culture-and-core-values-35776678396753</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, offering an in-depth look into the unique work culture at Binance, a company known for its high-performance and results-driven environment. The article aims to pr&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">daf3aaf08c81cd5459b7e939a27511dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to launch the ETHGas Trading Competition on Binance Alpha, offering exclusive token rewards to participants. The competition will be held in two promotion periods, with the first running from 2026-02-10 13:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-17 13:00 (UTC), and the second from 2026-02-17 13:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-24 13:00 (UTC). Participants will be ranked based on their total purchase volume of ETHGas (GWEI) tokens during each period. The top 2,000 users by purchase volume will share 3,760,000 GWEI tokens equally, with each eligible user receiving 1,880 GWEI tokens.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Only trades executed via Binance Wallet (Keyless) or Binance Alpha will qualify for the promotion, excluding third-party dApp transactions. The competition does not impose any volume caps, allowing participants to trade freely. However, token bridging transactions are not eligible, and trading volume from Alpha-to-Alpha token pairs will not count towards Alpha Points or competition rankings. Rewards will be distributed in GWEI tokens and will be claimable by eligible users before 2026-03-10 13:00:00 (UTC). Users must claim their rewards within 14 days after they become available, or they will be forfeited.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;To participate, users must click [Join] on the Binance App event page, ensuring their trading volume is counted. Participants are required to update their Binance App to the latest version and create a Binance Wallet (Keyless). Binance reserves the right to amend or cancel the activity at its discretion, and users must adhere to the terms and conditions governing the promotion. The competition is open to users with active Binance accounts, and rewards will not be distributed to those who deactivate their accounts or wallets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ Recalls $15 Billion Withdrawal Test as Binance Faced Market Panic in 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-recalls-15-billion-withdrawal-test-as-binance-faced-market-panic-in-2022-35789237088482</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), founder and former CEO of Binance, outlined how the exchange safeguards user funds during periods of extreme market volatility during a recent AMA session on Binance Square.Respon&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f36eabd1eb4c35ae2bac8b5f0b0d86e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to update the collateral ratio and Tiered Collateral Ratio for PM Pro concerning specific assets under Portfolio Margin. This adjustment is scheduled to take place on 2026-02-13 at 06:00 (UTC) and is expected to be completed within approximately 30 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The assets affected by this update include &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/W_USDT?contentId=290046053321041" target="_blank"&gt;W&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/SEI_USDT?contentId=290046053321041" target="_blank"&gt;SEI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/RUNE_USDT?contentId=290046053321041" target="_blank"&gt;RUNE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, SSV, BB, 1INCH, COMP, KSM, AR, PYTH, CKB, KMNO, KNC, DUSK, ATA, MAV, SPK, YFI, HEI, and IOTA. The collateral ratios for these assets will be reduced, with W and SEI decreasing from 45% to 40%, and others like RUNE, SSV, BB, 1INCH, COMP, KSM, AR, PYTH, and CKB dropping from 35% to 30%. Additionally, KMNO, KNC, DUSK, ATA, MAV, SPK, YFI, HEI, and IOTA will see their collateral ratios decrease from 20% to 10%.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;For PM Pro assets, the collateral ratio adjustments will also affect the rank floor and cap in USD. For &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/SSV_USDT?contentId=290046053321041" target="_blank"&gt;SSV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/BB_USDT?contentId=290046053321041" target="_blank"&gt;BB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/CKB_USDT?contentId=290046053321041" target="_blank"&gt;CKB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, the rank floor will change from 90 to 100,000 USD, maintaining a 100% collateral ratio. The cap will adjust from 100,000 to 250,000 USD, with the collateral ratio decreasing to 80%. Further adjustments include a cap increase to 500,000 USD with a 50% collateral ratio, and a cap of 99,999,999,999 USD with a 10% collateral ratio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance advises users to closely monitor the Unified Maintenance Margin Ratio (uniMMR) to prevent potential liquidation or losses due to these changes. The collateral ratio impacts the uniMMR, and users should remain vigilant to manage their positions effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ Says User Protection Remains Binance’s Top Priority Despite Market FUD</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-says-user-protection-remains-binance-s-top-priority-despite-market-fud-35788897767138</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;In a recent AMA session on Binance Square, Binance founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ) emphasized that the exchange continues to place user protection at the center of its operations, even amid ongoing market&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23301bf20ccf88a96c018e15c4afe244</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that a new feature will soon be available for users of Binance Wallet, allowing them to utilize their Binance Alpha Points in innovative ways. This update is expected to enhance the functionality of the platform, providing users with additional options for managing their digital assets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The introduction of this feature marks a significant development in the Binance ecosystem, as it aims to offer more flexibility and utility to its users. While specific details regarding the implementation and usage of Alpha Points have not been disclosed, the announcement has generated anticipation among the community. Users are eager to see how this update will impact their experience on the platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Alpha Points have been a part of the platform's reward system, encouraging user engagement and participation. With this upcoming update, Binance is set to expand the scope of these points, potentially offering new incentives and benefits to its users. The exact date of the rollout and further information about the feature are yet to be announced, but users are advised to stay informed through Binance's official channels for the latest updates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ Emphasizes the Reputation Risks of Engaging in Paid Attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-emphasizes-the-reputation-risks-of-engaging-in-paid-attacks-35789098214057</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;In a recent AMA session on Binance Square, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the founder and former CEO of Binance, discussed the recent wave of criticism directed at him, attributing much of it to what is known i&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54b44264156d3d0c2ecf19913fe630b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that it will host the 6th Pre-TGE Prime Sale Edition featuring Espresso Foundation (ESP) on its platform. The event is scheduled to take place on February 10, 2026, from 12:00 to 14:00 (UTC). This sale offers eligible users the opportunity to participate using their accumulated Binance Alpha Points.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Pre-TGE Prime Sale is designed for users who have earned Binance Alpha Points, allowing them to engage in the sale of ESP tokens. The specific details regarding the Pre-TGE event and the Event Portal will be released soon, providing participants with the necessary information to prepare for the sale. This initiative is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to offer unique opportunities for its community members to engage with new digital assets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants are encouraged to ensure they have the required Binance Alpha Points to take part in the sale. The event promises to be a significant opportunity for users interested in acquiring ESP tokens ahead of their general token generation event. As Binance continues to expand its offerings, events like the Pre-TGE Prime Sale play a crucial role in enhancing user engagement and providing access to emerging digital assets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Delist Multiple Margin Trading Pairs in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-to-delist-multiple-margin-trading-pairs-in-february-2026-35945221810802</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will delist several margin trading pairs on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC). The affected pairs include both cross and isolated margin pairs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2a8a4bd932504fc867e04028a93cf39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that SlowMist has successfully completed a comprehensive security audit of its wallet. The audit involved both manual analysis and automated tools to ensure the highest level of security. SlowMist approached the audit from an attacker’s perspective, meticulously examining both open-source and proprietary code to identify potential vulnerabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The security audit aimed to bolster the wallet's defenses against potential threats, ensuring that users can manage their digital assets with confidence. By reviewing the wallet's code thoroughly, SlowMist sought to uncover any weaknesses that could be exploited by malicious actors. This proactive measure underscores Binance's commitment to maintaining a secure platform for its users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The audit process involved a detailed examination of the wallet's architecture and functionality. SlowMist employed advanced techniques to simulate potential attack scenarios, providing a comprehensive assessment of the wallet's security posture. The findings from this audit will inform future enhancements to the wallet, further strengthening its security features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;This initiative reflects Binance's ongoing efforts to prioritize user security and trust. By collaborating with security experts like SlowMist, Binance aims to ensure that its platform remains resilient against evolving cyber threats. The completion of this audit marks a significant step in safeguarding user assets and maintaining the integrity of the Binance ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Delist Multiple Spot Trading Pairs in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-05-2026-binance-to-delist-multiple-spot-trading-pairs-in-february-2026-36038259194425</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will delist several spot trading pairs as part of its regular review process aimed at maintaining a high-quality trading environment. The decis&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98c0d5c48424bc435d351e712295871f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X the launch of USDD Campaign Season 3, offering participants the opportunity to unlock substantial rewards. The activity period for this campaign is set from 2026-02-09 00:00:00 to 2026-03-10 23:59:59 UTC. Participants can subscribe USDT into the USDT-sUSDD Strategy to share in $800,000 worth of USDD rewards. This initiative is designed to encourage active participation and reward loyalty among users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants from previous USDD campaigns who maintain their positions will remain eligible for Season 3 rewards, ensuring continuity and incentivizing long-term engagement. This campaign represents a significant opportunity for users to benefit from their involvement in the Binance ecosystem. By subscribing to the USDT-sUSDD Strategy, users can maximize their potential earnings and contribute to the dynamic environment fostered by Binance. The campaign underscores Binance's commitment to providing rewarding experiences for its community members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Delist Multiple Tokens Amid Periodic Review</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-02-2026-binance-to-delist-multiple-tokens-amid-periodic-review-35907392575826</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange has decided to delist several tokens following a comprehensive review of its digital assets. The tokens set for delisting include Acala Token (&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5673915da2da5323a6b3bed75e1645b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that it has introduced K-line charts in Pro Mode to enhance the trading experience for its users. This new feature aims to improve trading flow and assist in more informed decision-making by providing detailed visual data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The K-line charts, also known as candlestick charts, are a popular tool among traders for analyzing price movements over time. By incorporating these charts into Pro Mode, Binance seeks to offer a more comprehensive trading platform that caters to both novice and experienced traders. The charts provide insights into market trends, helping users to make better-informed trading decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;This enhancement is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to improve its platform and provide users with advanced tools for trading. The introduction of K-line charts in Pro Mode is expected to streamline the trading process, offering users a more efficient and effective way to analyze market data and execute trades. This update reflects Binance's commitment to continuously upgrading its services to meet the evolving needs of its user base.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches February Dual Investment Challenge with USDC Rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-launches-february-dual-investment-challenge-with-usdc-rewards-35940567448634</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced the February Monthly Challenge for Dual Investment users, offering rewards of up to 5,888 USDC and an additional 3,000 USDC. The&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">729e4eed06b27fe097178ea30dc2239d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that it has made significant improvements to its Earn market list, aiming to enhance readability and user experience. This update is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to streamline its platform and provide users with a more intuitive interface.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The updated Earn market list is designed to offer clearer insights into available earning opportunities, making it easier for users to navigate and select options that best suit their investment strategies. By refining the presentation of information, Binance seeks to facilitate a more efficient decision-making process for its users, ensuring they can quickly access the details they need.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;This enhancement reflects Binance's commitment to continuously improving its services and adapting to user feedback. The platform's focus on user experience is evident in this latest update, which aims to simplify the process of exploring and participating in various earning opportunities available on Binance. As the platform evolves, Binance remains dedicated to providing a seamless and user-friendly environment for its global community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Discontinue Czech Koruna Services and Delist USDC/CZK Pair</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-to-discontinue-czech-koruna-services-and-delist-usdc-czk-pair-35942410375449</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange will discontinue services related to the Czech Koruna (CZK) as part of its ongoing adjustments to trading offerings. The key change involves th&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b762547aa8e0ff06944c1be3b5b4fb71</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X the commencement of its Opinion Booster Program Phase 1, inviting users to participate in the initiative aimed at enhancing community engagement. The program is designed to gather valuable insights and feedback from participants, contributing to the platform's continuous improvement and development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Opinion Booster Program offers users the opportunity to share their thoughts and opinions on various aspects of Binance's services and features. Participants are encouraged to provide constructive feedback, which will be instrumental in shaping future updates and enhancements. This initiative underscores Binance's commitment to fostering a collaborative environment where user input is valued and considered in decision-making processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants in the program will have the chance to influence the direction of Binance's offerings, ensuring that the platform remains responsive to the needs and preferences of its community. By actively engaging with users, Binance aims to create a more user-centric experience, aligning its services with the expectations and requirements of its diverse user base. The program is open to all users, and further details on participation and feedback submission will be provided through Binance's official channels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Support United Stables (U) as Margin Asset in Multi-Assets Mode</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-futures-to-support-united-stables-u-as-margin-asset-in-multi-assets-mode-35943357612601</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, Binance Futures will integrate United Stables (U) as a margin asset within the Multi-Assets Mode starting from 2026-02-05 07:00 (UTC). This development allo&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdb1a914ebcd05b32b8de5d4e2fb2f77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that all Binance Wallet users have successfully unlocked the grand reward, which has been fully distributed in USDF to their Perpetuals accounts. This achievement marks a significant milestone for the community, showcasing the collective effort of users in reaching the reward target.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The distribution of USDF rewards to Perpetuals accounts highlights Binance's commitment to providing value to its users through engaging activities. The platform has confirmed that more exclusive perpetuals trading competitions are on the horizon for Binance Wallet users, promising further opportunities to participate and earn rewards. While specific details of these upcoming competitions have not been disclosed, users are encouraged to stay informed through Binance's official channels for future announcements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;This development underscores Binance's strategy to enhance user engagement by offering competitive and rewarding experiences. By distributing USDF rewards, Binance aims to incentivize active participation and foster a dynamic community within its ecosystem. As users anticipate the next round of competitions, Binance continues to innovate and expand its offerings, ensuring that its platform remains interactive and beneficial for all participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Adjust Interest Rates on INTCUSDT and HOODUSDT Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-to-adjust-interest-rates-on-intcusdt-and-hoodusdt-contracts-35948399275633</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the cryptocurrency exchange will implement changes to the interest rates of INTCUSDT and HOODUSDT Perpetual Contracts. Effective from 2026-02-03 16:15 (UTC)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b84ba06e32ab6f106a5211f8f1484d0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that Dynamic has successfully integrated the Binance Wallet Extension, aiming to streamline the connection between decentralized applications (dApps) and the Binance Wallet. This integration is designed to benefit both developers and users by providing a seamless experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;For developers, the integration with Dynamic allows for an effortless connection of their dApps to the Binance Wallet. This connection opens up access to millions of verified users, potentially expanding the reach and user base of their applications. The integration is expected to simplify the process for developers, enabling them to focus on enhancing their dApps without worrying about complex onboarding procedures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users, on the other hand, will experience a low-friction onboarding process when accessing their favorite dApps through the Binance Wallet. This ease of access is anticipated to enhance user experience by reducing barriers and making it more convenient to engage with various decentralized applications. The integration aims to provide a smooth and efficient way for users to interact with the blockchain ecosystem, leveraging the capabilities of the Binance Wallet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The announcement marks a significant step in improving the functionality and accessibility of dApps within the Binance ecosystem. By integrating with Dynamic, Binance continues to enhance its platform, offering users and developers more options and flexibility in managing digital assets and engaging with blockchain technology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Introduces Security Center to Enhance Wallet Protection</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-introduces-security-center-to-enhance-wallet-protection-35953470664073</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has unveiled a new Security Center within Binance Wallet, aimed at bolstering user asset protection by identifying and managing potential risks&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6884bf298157ec77e97ee054e43d60cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance founder and former CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) posted on X, expressing that Binance recorded net capital inflows across all major timeframes, countering claims of capital outflows circulating in the market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ stated that Binance saw net inflows over the past 1 day, 7 days, and 1 month, with total inflows amounting to billions of dollars, despite claims from some parties possibly associated with FUD narratives who have suggested the opposite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="css-jyb3wi" data-area="img"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-imgbox css-nuuble"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="mica-lazy-img css-182lng5" data-src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/dVnFuFWnLUmRTAKmynXZCC.png" src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/dVnFuFWnLUmRTAKmynXZCC.png"/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;﻿&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Suspend Sei Network Transactions for Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-to-suspend-sei-network-transactions-for-upgrade-35937801416305</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, starting on 2026-02-03 at 16:30 (UTC), the platform will temporarily suspend deposits and withdrawals of tokens on the Sei (SEI) network. This suspension is&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95125dfbc1177c3ff0f6197ff02c1118</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced new offers in its Yield Arena, providing users with opportunities to earn rewards through various products. The Earn Spotlight Limited-Time Offers include USDe, where eligible users holding at least 0.01 USDe for 24 hours can enjoy 4.5% APR rewards from 2026-01-30 00:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-05 23:59 (UTC). Additionally, Simple Earn offers users subscribing to KGST Flexible Products a 10% Bonus Tiered APR from 2026-02-03 00:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-16 23:59 (UTC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Dual Investment program, running from 2026-02-03 02:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-28 23:59 (UTC), allows users to participate in the Monthly Challenge program, offering up to $5,888 and $3,000 in additional rewards. Binance provides a range of flexible and locked products with varying APRs and subscription limits. For instance, USDT and USDC Flexible Products offer a real-time APR of approximately 1.5% with a 5% Bonus Tiered APR, while ETH Flexible Products offer a real-time APR of approximately 1.3% with a 0.1% Bonus Tiered APR. Locked Products such as SKY and NIL offer 12.75% and 29.9% APRs, respectively, over 90 and 120 days.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance reserves the right to adjust APRs without prior notice, and offers are available on a first-come, first-served basis. Users can redeem their assets in advance in Simple Earn Locked Products, with the principal returned to their Spot Accounts. Rewards from ongoing Launchpools are automatically received by users holding BNB Flexible and Locked Products positions. Additionally, users subscribing to BNB Simple Earn products can receive airdropped tokens via HODLer Airdrops. Simple Earn products are principal-protected, allowing users to earn rewards securely. Dual Investment offers high-yield structured products, enabling users to buy or sell cryptocurrency at a desired price and date while earning rewards regardless of market direction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Renews Partnership with Islamabad United for PSL Season 11</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-04-2026-binance-renews-partnership-with-islamabad-united-for-psl-season-11-35995866827034</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, announcing the renewal of its partnership with Islamabad United as the Official Crypto Exchange Partner for Pakistan Super League (PSL) Season 11. This collaborat&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8ae77cab21912334324c2e67d3b2392</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CoinMarketCap released its &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 2026 Mainstream Crypto Exchange Reserve Ranking Report&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; on Feb. 4, showing that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; continues to dominate global exchange reserves by a wide margin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the report, Binance ranked &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;first among mainstream crypto exchanges&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;total reserves of approximately $155.64 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, significantly ahead of its peers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="Stablecoins-and-Bitcoin-Anchor-Binances-Reserves"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Stablecoins and Bitcoin Anchor Binance’s Reserves&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The data shows that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;stablecoins account for about $47.47 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, representing &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;30.5% of Binance’s total reserves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, underscoring the platform’s strong liquidity position and ability to meet user withdrawals during periods of market stress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="css-jyb3wi" data-area="img"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-imgbox css-nuuble"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="mica-lazy-img css-182lng5" data-src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/5QGHQsZ6eTAhmD9VKe7AdT.png" src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/5QGHQsZ6eTAhmD9VKe7AdT.png"/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Bitcoin-related reserves totaled &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;approximately $49.84 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, making BTC the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;largest single asset category&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; on Binance’s balance sheet. This highlights the exchange’s continued central role in Bitcoin liquidity and settlement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="High-Liquidity-and-Diversified-Asset-Structure"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;High Liquidity and Diversified Asset Structure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CoinMarketCap noted that Binance’s overall reserve composition remains &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;highly liquid and well-diversified&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, balancing stablecoins, Bitcoin, and other major crypto assets. This structure is designed to support operational resilience, risk management, and user confidence amid volatile market conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The January 2026 report reinforces Binance’s position as the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;largest and most capitalized centralized crypto exchange&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, at a time when transparency around reserves and proof-of-assets remains a key focus for the industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Enhances Security with New Center</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-04-2026-binance-wallet-enhances-security-with-new-center-35999612519193</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X the introduction of a new Security Center within the Binance Wallet, aimed at enhancing user security by automatically checking for potential risks. This new feature allows user&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea183550922924493a73c519ae5d315f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X the introduction of a new Security Center within the Binance Wallet, aimed at enhancing user security by automatically checking for potential risks. This new feature allows users to manage security for both Keyless and imported wallets from a single hub, providing a streamlined approach to wallet management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Security Center is designed to offer users a comprehensive overview of their wallet's security status, identifying vulnerabilities and suggesting improvements. By centralizing security management, Binance aims to simplify the process for users, ensuring that they can easily monitor and address any security concerns. This initiative reflects Binance's ongoing commitment to safeguarding user assets and maintaining trust within its platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users are encouraged to regularly check their wallet security through the Security Center to ensure their assets remain protected. The feature is part of Binance's broader efforts to enhance security measures and provide users with the tools necessary to manage their digital assets effectively. As digital threats continue to evolve, Binance remains focused on developing solutions that address these challenges, reinforcing its position as a leader in the cryptocurrency industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Tops CoinMarketCap’s January 2026 Exchange Reserve Rankings With $155.6B in Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-04-2026-binance-tops-coinmarketcap-s-january-2026-exchange-reserve-rankings-with-155-6b-in-assets-35999886677618</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/5QGHQsZ6eTAhmD9VKe7AdT.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;CoinMarketCap released its January 2026 Mainstream Crypto Exchange Reserve Ranking Report on Feb. 4, showing that Binance continues to dominate global exchange reserves by a wide margin.According to t&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61f0bea171fc8fb3947b7f292b54e4fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, announcing the renewal of its partnership with Islamabad United as the Official Crypto Exchange Partner for Pakistan Super League (PSL) Season 11. This collaboration aims to continue fan-focused initiatives that advance blockchain education in Pakistan. The partnership builds on a successful inaugural collaboration in PSL Season 10, with Binance retaining its back-of-shirt jersey placement for the second consecutive year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance and Islamabad United are set to engage cricket fans across the country through initiatives that promote blockchain education, while also supporting Pakistan’s broader crypto community through responsible digital engagement. Pakistan remains a key market for Binance, home to a young, tech-savvy population increasingly exploring digital assets. Following Binance’s No-Objection Certificate from PVARA, this renewal reflects Binance’s long-term commitment to fostering a safe, sustainable crypto ecosystem in the country. Tarik Erk, Binance’s Regional Head for MENAT and Senior Executive Officer, Abu Dhabi, emphasized the cultural significance of cricket in Pakistan and expressed excitement about building on last year’s success to make blockchain technology accessible nationwide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;To celebrate the partnership renewal, Binance is offering new Pakistani users an exclusive welcome reward between February 4 and 15, 2026. New users who sign up through the Binance app using the referral code “MakeYourMove” and complete verification will receive PKR 1,000 to start exploring digital assets. This initiative aligns with Islamabad United’s commitment to innovation and excellence, as the team remains the most successful franchise in PSL history with three championship titles. The collaboration reflects a shared vision of making blockchain technology more accessible while supporting responsible engagement across Pakistan’s growing digital-asset ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The campaign is valid for specified dates only and is open to Pakistan residents. Only the first 1,000 winners will be rewarded, with up to 100 winners selected each day during the campaign period. Participants must be 18 years or older and eligible as per Binance Terms of Use. Only new Binance users registered during the campaign period qualify, and users must complete account verification to be eligible for rewards. Existing Binance users are not eligible. Rewards are limited, non-transferable, and not redeemable for cash. Binance reserves the right to substitute rewards of equal value if required, and any fraudulent activity, multiple accounts, or misuse will result in disqualification. Binance may suspend or terminate accounts found violating campaign rules, and winner selection is final and at Binance’s discretion. Participation implies acceptance of Binance’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Digital assets are subject to high market risk and price volatility, and Binance is not liable for any losses incurred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Unveils New Yield Arena Offers with Flexible and Locked Products</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-05-2026-binance-unveils-new-yield-arena-offers-with-flexible-and-locked-products-36036414026578</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced new offers in its Yield Arena, providing users with opportunities to earn rewards through various products. The Earn Spotlight L&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">016bf628dc7a72d05f77fd32702e735e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, starting on 2026-02-03 at 16:30 (UTC), the platform will temporarily suspend deposits and withdrawals of tokens on the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/SEI_USDT?contentId=35937801416305" target="_blank"&gt;Sei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (SEI) network. This suspension is to facilitate a network upgrade aimed at enhancing user experience. The upgrade is scheduled to occur at block height 192,196,147, approximately at 2026-02-03 17:30 (UTC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The trading of tokens on the Sei network will remain unaffected during this period. Binance assures users that it will manage all technical requirements related to the upgrade. Once the network is deemed stable post-upgrade, deposits and withdrawals will be reopened. No additional announcements will be made regarding the reopening of these services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: Binance Recorded Billions in Net Inflows Across All Key Timeframes</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-05-2026-cz-binance-recorded-billions-in-net-inflows-across-all-key-timeframes-36041243061529</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/dVnFuFWnLUmRTAKmynXZCC.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance founder and former CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) posted on X, expressing that Binance recorded net capital inflows across all major timeframes, countering claims of capital outflows circulating in t&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c1bc5602f69eb720431a85255e1ce8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has unveiled a new Security Center within Binance Wallet, aimed at bolstering user asset protection by identifying and managing potential risks. Central to this initiative is the Security Scan feature, which automatically examines wallets for security vulnerabilities and offers actionable recommendations to safeguard accounts. The Security Center consolidates existing security tools, such as backup, verification methods, approvals, and Secure Auto Sign, into a unified interface, simplifying the process for users to monitor and enhance their wallet security.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Security Scan feature is designed to detect security risks across various aspects of wallet management, including setup, assets, approvals, and transactions. It supports both Binance Keyless Wallets and wallets imported via seed phrases or private keys, allowing users to review and secure multiple wallets on a single platform. Detected issues are categorized by risk severity, enabling users to prioritize actions based on whether their wallet faces no issues, medium-risk issues, or high-risk issues. The scan checks for risks in several areas: Wallet Security, which monitors backup status and operating environment; Asset Security, which flags tokens and assets with elevated risk; Approval Security, which identifies dangerous or excessive permissions; and Transaction Security, which examines transaction history to detect potential threats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users receive immediate alerts on the homepage when potential risks are identified, accompanied by clear recommendations for action. For instance, if a wallet approval list contains an unrecognized token or risky permission, the Security Center will highlight it, providing guidance on steps such as revoking the approval. Automated scans continuously monitor wallets to proactively identify threats, ensuring security without manual intervention. Binance emphasizes that Security Scan results are informational and do not constitute financial advice, urging users to conduct their own research and consult financial advisers as needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Integrates Binance Wallet Extension for Enhanced dApp Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-05-2026-dynamic-integrates-binance-wallet-extension-for-enhanced-dapp-connectivity-36042064548801</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that Dynamic has successfully integrated the Binance Wallet Extension, aiming to streamline the connection between decentralized applications (dApps) and the Binance Wallet. Thi&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d9fdb09a9b70e3d20078625ee4148a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the cryptocurrency exchange will implement changes to the interest rates of INTCUSDT and HOODUSDT Perpetual Contracts. Effective from 2026-02-03 16:15 (UTC), the interest rate component of the funding rate for these contracts will be set to 0%. This adjustment is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to optimize its product and service offerings for users globally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The funding rate, a crucial element in perpetual contracts, consists of two components: the interest rate and the premium. The formula for calculating the funding rate is: Funding Rate (F) = [Average Premium Index (P) + clamp (interest rate - Premium Index (P), 0.05%, -0.05%)] / (8 / N). While the interest rate will be set to 0%, the funding rate may still fluctuate based on the premium index, which becomes the sole influencing factor under these conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users interested in monitoring the latest funding rate and interest rate can access the Real-Time Funding Rate page. Additionally, API users have the option to query USDⓈ-M futures funding rate information through the newly added endpoint: GET /fapi/v1/fundingInfo. This change underscores Binance's commitment to providing a seamless trading experience by regularly reviewing and adjusting its offerings. The exchange advises users to stay informed about these updates to make well-informed trading decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Users Receive USDF Rewards After Successful Unlock</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-05-2026-binance-wallet-users-receive-usdf-rewards-after-successful-unlock-36049641221802</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that all Binance Wallet users have successfully unlocked the grand reward, which has been fully distributed in USDF to their Perpetuals accounts. This achievement marks a signif&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">904ca9efbb175d36cc672d103194ce9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, Binance Futures will integrate United Stables (U) as a margin asset within the Multi-Assets Mode starting from 2026-02-05 07:00 (UTC). This development allows users to utilize U as a margin asset, enhancing the flexibility of trading strategies on the platform. The maximum transfer-in limits for U as a margin asset are contingent upon users' VIP levels, which can be reviewed on the Multi-Assets Info page for further details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The haircut rates for U in an Auto-Exchange are established at 1%, and U margin balances are calculated based on the U price index in real time. Binance retains the authority to modify maximum transfer-in limits and haircut rates in response to market conditions. This adjustment aims to ensure optimal trading conditions and risk management for users engaging in futures trading.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance emphasizes the importance of referring to the original English version of the announcement for the most accurate information, as there may be discrepancies between translated versions. The integration of United Stables (U) as a margin asset marks a significant enhancement in Binance Futures' offerings, providing users with more options for managing their digital assets effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches Opinion Booster Program Phase 1</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-06-2026-binance-launches-opinion-booster-program-phase-1-36075662317906</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X the commencement of its Opinion Booster Program Phase 1, inviting users to participate in the initiative aimed at enhancing community engagement. The program is designed to gath&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19b896e35a555fc869c34c5c12384177</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange will discontinue services related to the Czech Koruna (CZK) as part of its ongoing adjustments to trading offerings. The key change involves the delisting of the USDC/CZK trading pair from Binance Spot, which is scheduled to occur on 2026-02-05 at 08:00 (UTC). Following this delisting, any remaining CZK balances in users' Binance accounts will no longer be available for spot trading. Additionally, all open spot orders for the USDC/CZK pair will be automatically closed once trading ceases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Despite the discontinuation of CZK services in spot trading, users will still have the option to purchase cryptocurrencies using their CZK balances through Binance's Buy Crypto and Convert features. Furthermore, Binance's Peer-to-Peer (P2P) services will remain operational without any changes, allowing users to continue trading in a decentralized manner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;USDC, the e-money token involved in this change, is issued by Circle Internet Financial Europe SAS. Holders of USDC have a legal claim against Circle SAS, the EU issuer, and are entitled to request redemption of their USDC at any time and at par value. This ensures that users can maintain confidence in the value of their holdings despite the changes in trading pair availability. The decision to discontinue CZK services reflects Binance's strategic adjustments to its platform offerings, aiming to streamline operations and focus on more widely used trading pairs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Enhances Earn Market List for Improved User Experience</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-06-2026-binance-enhances-earn-market-list-for-improved-user-experience-288706118332529</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that it has made significant improvements to its Earn market list, aiming to enhance readability and user experience. This update is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to streaml&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83478a1a31e438521c8c36becfa95619</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced the February Monthly Challenge for Dual Investment users, offering rewards of up to 5,888 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/USDC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;USDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; and an additional 3,000 USDC. The promotion runs from 2026-02-03 02:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-28 23:59 (UTC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Promotion A: Monthly Leaderboard**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants in the Dual Investment program will be ranked based on their average subscription amount during the promotion period. To qualify, the subscription period must exceed seven days. The top 100 users will receive rewards, with the first place earning 5,888 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/USDC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;USDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;. Other rewards include 2,188 USDC for second and third places, 1,088 USDC for fourth and fifth places, and decreasing amounts for subsequent ranks down to 68 USDC for those ranked 71st to 100th.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Promotion B: Additional Subscription Rewards**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users who subscribe to an average Dual Investment amount exceeding $5,000,000 will receive an additional 100 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/USDC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;USDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; for every extra $100,000 subscribed. The subscription period must also be more than seven days. For example, if a user's average subscription is $5,500,000, they will receive 500 USDC as a reward. The maximum reward cap per user is 3,000 USDC. Rewards from both promotions can be earned simultaneously.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**About Dual Investment**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Dual Investment is a structured product allowing users to buy or sell cryptocurrency at a future price and date while earning rewards. It supports tokens like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/BTC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;BTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/ETH_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;ETH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/SOL_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;SOL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, and BNB, with an annual percentage rate (APR) of 15% or more. Users must complete identity verification to participate, and rewards will be distributed within 14 days after the promotion ends. Binance reserves the right to amend terms and conditions at its discretion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Enhances Trading with Pro Mode K-Line Charts</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-06-2026-binance-enhances-trading-with-pro-mode-k-line-charts-288706085372017</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that it has introduced K-line charts in Pro Mode to enhance the trading experience for its users. This new feature aims to improve trading flow and assist in more informed decis&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ade9e98f041c5cc1d8f802357772e361</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange has decided to delist several tokens following a comprehensive review of its digital assets. The tokens set for delisting include Acala Token (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/ACA_USDT?contentId=35907392575826" target="_blank"&gt;ACA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/CHESS_USDT?contentId=35907392575826" target="_blank"&gt;Tranchess&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (CHESS), Streamr (DATA), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/DF_USDT?contentId=35907392575826" target="_blank"&gt;dForce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (DF), Aavegotchi (GHST), and NKN (NKN). The delisting process will commence on 2026-02-13 at 03:00 (UTC), with all spot trading pairs for these tokens being removed. Binance emphasizes that the decision is part of its ongoing efforts to ensure high standards and adapt to changing market dynamics. Factors influencing the delisting include the commitment of the project team, development activity, trading volume, network stability, community engagement, and regulatory compliance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The delisting will affect various Binance services, including Trading Bots, Spot Copy Trading, and Binance Futures. Users are advised to update or cancel their trading strategies and positions to avoid potential losses. Binance Spot Copy Trading will delist the tokens on 2026-02-06 at 03:00 (UTC), and Binance Futures will close all positions and conduct automatic settlements on the contracts by 2026-02-06 at 09:00 (UTC). Additionally, Binance Simple Earn will delist the tokens after 2026-02-09 at 07:00 (UTC), and Dual Investment will cease support for these tokens starting the subsequent Friday at 08:00 (UTC). Binance Pool will stop mining support for these tokens on 2026-02-06 at 03:00 (UTC), and users are encouraged to halt mining activities to prevent losses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Margin will also delist the tokens from Cross and Isolated Margin on 2026-02-06 at 10:00 (UTC). Users are advised to manage their margin accounts and transfer assets to Spot Accounts before the delisting time. Portfolio Margin users should monitor their Unified Maintenance Margin Ratio closely to avoid liquidation risks. Binance Convert will delist the tokens and associated pairs on 2026-02-13 at 02:00 (UTC), while Binance Buy &amp;amp; Sell Crypto will remove them on 2026-02-03 at 03:00 (UTC). Other services like Gift Card and Binance Pay will also cease support for these tokens by the specified dates. Users are encouraged to manage their assets accordingly to avoid inconveniences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Announces USDD Campaign Season 3 with $800,000 Rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-06-2026-binance-announces-usdd-campaign-season-3-with-800-000-rewards-288744969035890</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X the launch of USDD Campaign Season 3, offering participants the opportunity to unlock substantial rewards. The activity period for this campaign is set from 2026-02-09 00:00:00&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeee1520721e5b9d4a6efd2498fa7d84</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will delist several spot trading pairs as part of its regular review process aimed at maintaining a high-quality trading environment. The decision to remove these pairs is based on factors such as poor liquidity and low trading volume. The affected trading pairs will be removed on 2026-02-06 at 08:00 (UTC). The pairs set for delisting include AUDIO/BTC, BB/FDUSD, BERA/FDUSD, EIGEN/BTC, FIDA/BTC, HEI/BTC, IOTX/ETH, KERNEL/FDUSD, MANTA/BTC, MTL/BTC, NEAR/FDUSD, PEOPLE/FDUSD, RENDER/FDUSD, RONIN/BTC, SAPIEN/BNB, SCR/BTC, S/ETH, S/FDUSD, SUSHI/BTC, and VANA/FDUSD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The delisting of these spot trading pairs will not affect the availability of the tokens on Binance Spot. Users will still have the option to trade the base and quote assets of these pairs through other available trading pairs on the platform. Additionally, Binance will terminate Spot Trading Bots services for the mentioned pairs at the same time. Users are advised to update or cancel their Spot Trading Bots before the cessation of services to prevent potential losses. This action is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to ensure a robust trading environment for its users. The platform encourages users to stay informed about delisting procedures and guidelines to manage their trading activities effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowMist Completes Security Audit of Binance Wallet</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-06-2026-slowmist-completes-security-audit-of-binance-wallet-288769679176882</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that SlowMist has successfully completed a comprehensive security audit of its wallet. The audit involved both manual analysis and automated tools to ensure the highest level of&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9f493bdb179904de90a49670d1edd49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will delist several margin trading pairs on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC). The affected pairs include both cross and isolated margin pairs. For cross margin pairs, the delisted pairs are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/KNC_USDT?contentId=35945221810802" target="_blank"&gt;KNC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/BTC_USDT?contentId=35945221810802" target="_blank"&gt;BTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/COTI_USDT?contentId=35945221810802" target="_blank"&gt;COTI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;/BTC, BAT/BTC, DUSK/BTC, RLC/BTC, GRT/ETH, GLM/BTC, and KAVA/BTC. The isolated margin pairs to be removed are KNC/BTC, COTI/BTC, BAT/BTC, DUSK/BTC, JST/BTC, RLC/BTC, GRT/ETH, GLM/BTC, KAVA/BTC, and CTK/BTC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Effective immediately, users will not be able to transfer any assets of the mentioned pairs into their Isolated Margin accounts via manual transfers or Auto-Transfer Mode. Users with outstanding liabilities in these tokens can only transfer up to the amount of their liabilities, minus any collateral already available. On February 4, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC), Binance Margin will suspend isolated margin borrowing for these pairs. Subsequently, on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC), Binance Margin will close users’ positions, conduct automatic settlements, and cancel all pending orders for the specified cross and isolated margin pairs. These pairs will then be removed from Binance Margin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users are advised to close their positions and transfer their assets from Margin Accounts to Spot Accounts before the cessation of Margin trading on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC). The delisting process may take approximately three hours, during which users will not be able to update their positions. Binance emphasizes that it will not be responsible for any potential losses incurred during this process. Users can continue trading the affected assets on other available trading pairs on Binance Margin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet to Host 6th Pre-TGE Prime Sale Featuring Espresso Foundation (ESP)</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-09-2026-binance-wallet-to-host-6th-pre-tge-prime-sale-featuring-espresso-foundation-esp-289766144826977</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that it will host the 6th Pre-TGE Prime Sale Edition featuring Espresso Foundation (ESP) on its platform. The event is scheduled to take place on February 10, 2026, from 12:00 t&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69ce2d1efdebcc3b367bf9c5d95aba30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In a recent AMA session on Binance Square, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the founder and former CEO of Binance, discussed the recent wave of criticism directed at him, attributing much of it to what is known in Chinese as “shui jun” (水军), or “water army” — paid accounts often funded by competitors to spread false information or attacks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ warned the community to be cautious of such accounts, which typically have low followers and are newly created. He also advised influencers not to damage their reputations by participating in paid attacks, as it is a net long-term loss.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ further noted that some negative feedback comes from traders who lost money recently and are looking for someone to blame. He emphasized personal responsibility in trading decisions: “You press the buy button, you press the sell button. You need to be responsible for that action. Just because the button is there, doesn’t mean you need to push it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet to Introduce New Use for Alpha Points</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-09-2026-binance-wallet-to-introduce-new-use-for-alpha-points-289802803034994</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that a new feature will soon be available for users of Binance Wallet, allowing them to utilize their Binance Alpha Points in innovative ways. This update is expected to enhance&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b42416ced31ef02b34ad98f87b8f61f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In a recent AMA session on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance Square&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, Binance founder &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; emphasized that the exchange continues to place user protection at the center of its operations, even amid ongoing market uncertainty and external criticism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ stated that Binance consistently goes “above and beyond” industry standards to safeguard users’ assets, data, and trading environment — a commitment he says is reflected in the platform’s long-term growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to CZ, Binance has now surpassed &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;300 million users globally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, highlighting sustained trust from the crypto community despite periods of intense FUD across the industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;He added that Binance’s focus remains on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;security, compliance, transparency, and product resilience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, rather than short-term narratives or market noise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Update Collateral Ratios for Portfolio Margin Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/290046053321041</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to update the collateral ratio and Tiered Collateral Ratio for PM Pro concerning specific assets under Portfolio Margin. This adjustment&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a40416ccd75a2be81f2d7d3e22eb80ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), founder and former CEO of Binance, outlined how the exchange safeguards user funds during periods of extreme market volatility during a recent AMA session on Binance Square.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Responding to questions about user protection during market turmoil, CZ emphasized that Binance operates as a fully reserved exchange supported by transparent, auditable systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“Binance has proof of reserves. We are fully reserved,” CZ said. “Balances are audited, and everything is easy to track.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="Proof-of-Reserves-and-Transparency-at-the-Core"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Proof of Reserves and Transparency at the Core&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ highlighted transparency as one of Binance’s defining principles, noting that the exchange’s on-chain proof-of-reserves framework allows users and analysts to verify holdings independently.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“We are the best in transparency,” he said, adding that public blockchain infrastructure makes asset tracking significantly easier compared with traditional financial systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Proof of reserves became a central focus across the crypto industry following a series of exchange failures, increasing user demand for verifiable custody models.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="December-2022-A-Major-Stress-Test-for-Binance"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;December 2022: A Major Stress Test for Binance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ referenced December 2022 as a critical moment that tested Binance’s infrastructure and liquidity resilience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;During that period, Binance processed more than &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$15 billion in withdrawals within a single week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, while the exchange’s total reserves stood at approximately &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$16 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; at the time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;At the peak of market stress, CZ said Binance handled &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;around $7 billion in withdrawals in a single day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; without disruption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“These were real stress tests,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="As-Long-as-the-System-Is-Working-Its-Working"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;‘As Long as the System Is Working, It’s Working’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ recalled that during the height of the withdrawal surge, he remained calm due to confidence in Binance’s reserve model and technical systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“I remember that time very clearly,” he said. “I was still managing Binance. I was having dinner with friends, and they asked why I wasn’t busy.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;His response, he explained, was simple: as long as systems function properly, operations continue normally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“As long as the system is working, it is working,” CZ said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches ETHGas Trading Competition with Token Rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-10-2026-binance-launches-ethgas-trading-competition-with-token-rewards-290119763305202</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to launch the ETHGas Trading Competition on Binance Alpha, offering exclusive token rewards to participants. The competition will be hel&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d789af9218a6efe53d06fcf55d31316</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, offering an in-depth look into the unique work culture at Binance, a company known for its high-performance and results-driven environment. The article aims to provide potential employees with a realistic perspective on what it means to work at Binance, emphasizing the company's five core values: protecting users, reducing friction, staying fast and autonomous, taking direct feedback, and collaborating globally without unnecessary meetings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The article begins by highlighting the freedom that comes with working at Binance, which operates on a global and remote-first basis. Employees are expected to adapt to different time zones, which can be challenging for those who prefer a structured 9-5 schedule. However, this freedom allows employees to manage their schedules and outputs, creating a work rhythm that suits their personal lives. This autonomy comes with accountability, as employees are trusted to own their time, outcomes, and impact. For those who thrive in a flexible environment and can handle the responsibility that comes with it, Binance offers a unique opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Humility is another core value at Binance, where employees are encouraged to take ownership and make decisions independently. This environment can be intense, as it requires individuals to handle complex tasks, address issues, and remain open to feedback, even when it is direct and unfiltered. The article emphasizes the importance of humility in accepting feedback, learning from mistakes, and improving work quality. This approach fosters a culture of continuous improvement and collaboration, where employees are expected to focus on outcomes rather than personal pride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Collaboration at Binance is characterized by a flat hierarchy, where teams are empowered to make decisions quickly and efficiently. The company values straightforward communication, shared goals, and a bias toward action. Employees are encouraged to document decisions and move work forward in a way that others can build upon, fostering trust and collaboration even in an asynchronous environment. This approach may feel unfamiliar to those accustomed to strict chains of command, but it allows for rapid progress and innovation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The 'Hardcore' value at Binance reflects the fast-paced nature of the cryptocurrency industry, where employees are expected to learn quickly, iterate, and adapt to uncertainty. The article describes how employees are encouraged to tackle high-impact problems, deliver initial solutions, and continuously improve them. This mindset requires resilience, curiosity, and a focus on outcomes, as the ultimate goal is to serve the users effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Finally, the article underscores the importance of being user-focused, as Binance's mission is to create products that are genuinely useful and secure for users. Employees are expected to prioritize user satisfaction, ensuring clarity, removing friction, and maintaining trust. This user-centric approach is the driving force behind Binance's operations, and those who share this commitment will find a fulfilling role within the company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In conclusion, the article makes it clear that Binance is not for everyone. It is a place for individuals who are ready to embrace high standards, take real ownership, and make a tangible impact in the world. Those seeking comfort and predictability may find other environments more suitable, but for builders who thrive on challenge and innovation, Binance offers a unique and rewarding opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet to Host Espresso Prime Sale for Alpha Point Holders</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-10-2026-binance-wallet-to-host-espresso-prime-sale-for-alpha-point-holders-290128100635745</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that users of Binance Wallet who possess 240 or more Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the upcoming Pre-TGE Prime Sale event for Espresso. This event can be ac&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b9ec31841e49e6525b6e3360fabe3c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance published an open letter to the crypto community on Binance Blog, and announced that market volatility and pressures have impacted the company alongside the broader industry, reflecting the increasing complexity of the crypto ecosystem and rising demands for governance, risk management, and accountability. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Throughout 2025, Binance focused on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; risk control, compliance cooperation, and ecosystem development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;: assisting users in recovering 38,648 incorrect deposits totaling $48 million, with cumulative recoveries exceeding $1.09 billion;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; helping 5.4 million users identify potential risks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;preventing approximately $6.69 billion in scam-related losses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;; collaborating with global law enforcement agencies to confiscate $131 million in illicit funds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance’s spot listing program covered 21 public blockchains&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, including 13 newly launched chains spanning payment, gaming, social, and other use cases. By the end of 2025, Binance’s proof-of-reserves demonstrated full backing of user assets totaling approximately $162.8 billion across 45 crypto assets. Binance remains committed to responding to market concerns through concrete actions and promoting sustainable industry growth. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance also announced plans to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;convert its $100 million SAFU fund stablecoin reserves into Bitcoin within 30 days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; of the announcement, with a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; rebalancing mechanism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; to maintain the fund’s value above $80 million amid Bitcoin price fluctuations. Binance will continue to uphold transparency, openness, and long-term commitment to advancing the crypto industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Earn Teases Upcoming Announcement</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-10-2026-binance-wallet-earn-teases-upcoming-announcement-290173153786593</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that something significant is on the horizon for users of Binance Wallet Earn. The platform has hinted at an upcoming development, urging users to stay engaged and attentive to&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d5763db7693b51f74af6c3017306b45</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), Binance founder and former CEO, posted on X stating that this is not the first time—and won’t be the last—that he has faced FUD attacks. He noted that tonight’s AMA will take a deeper look into why and how these attacks occur. CZ added, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;"While our (self-perceived) 'competitors' focus on us, we continue to build and grow."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ will host an Binance Square English livestream AMA at 8:00 PM (GMT+4, Dubai time) on January 30, 2026.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="css-jyb3wi" data-area="img"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-imgbox css-nuuble"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="mica-lazy-img css-182lng5" data-src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/9sBULXe2DY4qtTSEjhxTvn.png" src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/9sBULXe2DY4qtTSEjhxTvn.png"/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
  </channel>
</rss>