<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Binance Square News</title>
    <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square</link>
    <description>Latest news from Binance Square with full content</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Binance Square RSS Generator</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:40:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches Season 2 of On-Chain Trade &amp; Win Campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-18-2026-binance-launches-season-2-of-on-chain-trade-win-campaign-35241997624490</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced the "On-Chain Trade &amp; Win Campaign" Season 2, offering participants the chance to compete and win rewards through on-chain tradi&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab948d77f75e0da9e5c38425d45c3349</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced the February Monthly Challenge for Dual Investment users, offering rewards of up to 5,888 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/USDC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;USDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; and an additional 3,000 USDC. The promotion runs from 2026-02-03 02:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-28 23:59 (UTC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Promotion A: Monthly Leaderboard**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants in the Dual Investment program will be ranked based on their average subscription amount during the promotion period. To qualify, the subscription period must exceed seven days. The top 100 users will receive rewards, with the first place earning 5,888 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/USDC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;USDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;. Other rewards include 2,188 USDC for second and third places, 1,088 USDC for fourth and fifth places, and decreasing amounts for subsequent ranks down to 68 USDC for those ranked 71st to 100th.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Promotion B: Additional Subscription Rewards**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users who subscribe to an average Dual Investment amount exceeding $5,000,000 will receive an additional 100 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/USDC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;USDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; for every extra $100,000 subscribed. The subscription period must also be more than seven days. For example, if a user's average subscription is $5,500,000, they will receive 500 USDC as a reward. The maximum reward cap per user is 3,000 USDC. Rewards from both promotions can be earned simultaneously.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**About Dual Investment**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Dual Investment is a structured product allowing users to buy or sell cryptocurrency at a future price and date while earning rewards. It supports tokens like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/BTC_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;BTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/ETH_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;ETH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/SOL_USDT?contentId=35940567448634" target="_blank"&gt;SOL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, and BNB, with an annual percentage rate (APR) of 15% or more. Users must complete identity verification to participate, and rewards will be distributed within 14 days after the promotion ends. Binance reserves the right to amend terms and conditions at its discretion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Reduces USD Withdrawal Fees via SWIFT Bank Transfer</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-19-2026-binance-reduces-usd-withdrawal-fees-via-swift-bank-transfer-35288076632289</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has implemented a significant reduction in transaction fees for USD withdrawals via SWIFT bank transfer. This change is effective immediately a&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9a18bf9bb55cc5985f7ab598f0174e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange has decided to delist several tokens following a comprehensive review of its digital assets. The tokens set for delisting include Acala Token (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/ACA_USDT?contentId=35907392575826" target="_blank"&gt;ACA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/CHESS_USDT?contentId=35907392575826" target="_blank"&gt;Tranchess&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (CHESS), Streamr (DATA), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/DF_USDT?contentId=35907392575826" target="_blank"&gt;dForce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (DF), Aavegotchi (GHST), and NKN (NKN). The delisting process will commence on 2026-02-13 at 03:00 (UTC), with all spot trading pairs for these tokens being removed. Binance emphasizes that the decision is part of its ongoing efforts to ensure high standards and adapt to changing market dynamics. Factors influencing the delisting include the commitment of the project team, development activity, trading volume, network stability, community engagement, and regulatory compliance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The delisting will affect various Binance services, including Trading Bots, Spot Copy Trading, and Binance Futures. Users are advised to update or cancel their trading strategies and positions to avoid potential losses. Binance Spot Copy Trading will delist the tokens on 2026-02-06 at 03:00 (UTC), and Binance Futures will close all positions and conduct automatic settlements on the contracts by 2026-02-06 at 09:00 (UTC). Additionally, Binance Simple Earn will delist the tokens after 2026-02-09 at 07:00 (UTC), and Dual Investment will cease support for these tokens starting the subsequent Friday at 08:00 (UTC). Binance Pool will stop mining support for these tokens on 2026-02-06 at 03:00 (UTC), and users are encouraged to halt mining activities to prevent losses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Margin will also delist the tokens from Cross and Isolated Margin on 2026-02-06 at 10:00 (UTC). Users are advised to manage their margin accounts and transfer assets to Spot Accounts before the delisting time. Portfolio Margin users should monitor their Unified Maintenance Margin Ratio closely to avoid liquidation risks. Binance Convert will delist the tokens and associated pairs on 2026-02-13 at 02:00 (UTC), while Binance Buy &amp;amp; Sell Crypto will remove them on 2026-02-03 at 03:00 (UTC). Other services like Gift Card and Binance Pay will also cease support for these tokens by the specified dates. Users are encouraged to manage their assets accordingly to avoid inconveniences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Launch BTC/U and LTC/USD1 Trading Pairs with Zero Fee Promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-19-2026-binance-to-launch-btc-u-and-ltc-usd1-trading-pairs-with-zero-fee-promotions-35286232853161</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to expand its trading options by introducing new trading pairs and promotional offers. Binance will open trading for BTC/U and LTC/USD1&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b7d458f183f6c33109621936398a031</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will delist several margin trading pairs on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC). The affected pairs include both cross and isolated margin pairs. For cross margin pairs, the delisted pairs are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/KNC_USDT?contentId=35945221810802" target="_blank"&gt;KNC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/BTC_USDT?contentId=35945221810802" target="_blank"&gt;BTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/COTI_USDT?contentId=35945221810802" target="_blank"&gt;COTI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;/BTC, BAT/BTC, DUSK/BTC, RLC/BTC, GRT/ETH, GLM/BTC, and KAVA/BTC. The isolated margin pairs to be removed are KNC/BTC, COTI/BTC, BAT/BTC, DUSK/BTC, JST/BTC, RLC/BTC, GRT/ETH, GLM/BTC, KAVA/BTC, and CTK/BTC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Effective immediately, users will not be able to transfer any assets of the mentioned pairs into their Isolated Margin accounts via manual transfers or Auto-Transfer Mode. Users with outstanding liabilities in these tokens can only transfer up to the amount of their liabilities, minus any collateral already available. On February 4, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC), Binance Margin will suspend isolated margin borrowing for these pairs. Subsequently, on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC), Binance Margin will close users’ positions, conduct automatic settlements, and cancel all pending orders for the specified cross and isolated margin pairs. These pairs will then be removed from Binance Margin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users are advised to close their positions and transfer their assets from Margin Accounts to Spot Accounts before the cessation of Margin trading on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC). The delisting process may take approximately three hours, during which users will not be able to update their positions. Binance emphasizes that it will not be responsible for any potential losses incurred during this process. Users can continue trading the affected assets on other available trading pairs on Binance Margin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha to Launch HeyElsa (ELSA) Trading on January 20, Airdrop Details Announced</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-20-2026-binance-alpha-to-launch-heyelsa-elsa-trading-on-january-20-airdrop-details-announced-35328389191618</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/image/pgc/202601/fKHa7fHEdR6XccQfwSh34b.jpeg" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Alpha will be the first platform to feature HeyElsa (ELSA), with Alpha trading scheduled to open on January 20, 2026, at 08:00 (UTC).Following the trading launch, eligible users will be able t&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a052c8b9ede9ae19705d3e465caa8e89</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange will discontinue services related to the Czech Koruna (CZK) as part of its ongoing adjustments to trading offerings. The key change involves the delisting of the USDC/CZK trading pair from Binance Spot, which is scheduled to occur on 2026-02-05 at 08:00 (UTC). Following this delisting, any remaining CZK balances in users' Binance accounts will no longer be available for spot trading. Additionally, all open spot orders for the USDC/CZK pair will be automatically closed once trading ceases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Despite the discontinuation of CZK services in spot trading, users will still have the option to purchase cryptocurrencies using their CZK balances through Binance's Buy Crypto and Convert features. Furthermore, Binance's Peer-to-Peer (P2P) services will remain operational without any changes, allowing users to continue trading in a decentralized manner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;USDC, the e-money token involved in this change, is issued by Circle Internet Financial Europe SAS. Holders of USDC have a legal claim against Circle SAS, the EU issuer, and are entitled to request redemption of their USDC at any time and at par value. This ensures that users can maintain confidence in the value of their holdings despite the changes in trading pair availability. The decision to discontinue CZK services reflects Binance's strategic adjustments to its platform offerings, aiming to streamline operations and focus on more widely used trading pairs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Update Collateral Ratios for Portfolio Margin</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-20-2026-binance-to-update-collateral-ratios-for-portfolio-margin-35334156563625</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will implement updates to the collateral ratio and Tiered Collateral Ratio for PM Pro concerning specific assets under Portfolio Margin. This u&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbab4e3fa13175eb5dbe00f651c92fd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In a recent AMA session on Binance Square, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the founder and former CEO of Binance, discussed the recent wave of criticism directed at him, attributing much of it to what is known in Chinese as “shui jun” (水军), or “water army” — paid accounts often funded by competitors to spread false information or attacks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ warned the community to be cautious of such accounts, which typically have low followers and are newly created. He also advised influencers not to damage their reputations by participating in paid attacks, as it is a net long-term loss.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ further noted that some negative feedback comes from traders who lost money recently and are looking for someone to blame. He emphasized personal responsibility in trading decisions: “You press the buy button, you press the sell button. You need to be responsible for that action. Just because the button is there, doesn’t mean you need to push it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Account Takeover Attacks and Binance's Defense Strategies</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-20-2026-understanding-account-takeover-attacks-and-binance-s-defense-strategies-35337994576098</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, revealing insights into the growing threat of account takeover attacks and how Binance is addressing these challenges. Account takeover attacks can lead to altere&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4eb8313e8346912c2389eee7b483059</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In a recent AMA session on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance Square&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, Binance founder &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; emphasized that the exchange continues to place user protection at the center of its operations, even amid ongoing market uncertainty and external criticism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ stated that Binance consistently goes “above and beyond” industry standards to safeguard users’ assets, data, and trading environment — a commitment he says is reflected in the platform’s long-term growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to CZ, Binance has now surpassed &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;300 million users globally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, highlighting sustained trust from the crypto community despite periods of intense FUD across the industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;He added that Binance’s focus remains on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;security, compliance, transparency, and product resilience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, rather than short-term narratives or market noise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Launch AIAUSDT Perpetual Contract with 20x Leverage</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-20-2026-binance-futures-to-launch-aiausdt-perpetual-contract-with-20x-leverage-35334978577746</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, Binance Futures is set to introduce the AIAUSDT Perpetual Contract on January 20, 2026, at 11:15 (UTC). This new contract will offer up to 20x leverage, aim&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44d0a3dda2e96221dd08fdf6ee1d859f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), founder and former CEO of Binance, outlined how the exchange safeguards user funds during periods of extreme market volatility during a recent AMA session on Binance Square.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Responding to questions about user protection during market turmoil, CZ emphasized that Binance operates as a fully reserved exchange supported by transparent, auditable systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“Binance has proof of reserves. We are fully reserved,” CZ said. “Balances are audited, and everything is easy to track.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="Proof-of-Reserves-and-Transparency-at-the-Core"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Proof of Reserves and Transparency at the Core&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ highlighted transparency as one of Binance’s defining principles, noting that the exchange’s on-chain proof-of-reserves framework allows users and analysts to verify holdings independently.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“We are the best in transparency,” he said, adding that public blockchain infrastructure makes asset tracking significantly easier compared with traditional financial systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Proof of reserves became a central focus across the crypto industry following a series of exchange failures, increasing user demand for verifiable custody models.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="December-2022-A-Major-Stress-Test-for-Binance"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;December 2022: A Major Stress Test for Binance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ referenced December 2022 as a critical moment that tested Binance’s infrastructure and liquidity resilience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;During that period, Binance processed more than &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$15 billion in withdrawals within a single week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, while the exchange’s total reserves stood at approximately &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$16 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; at the time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;At the peak of market stress, CZ said Binance handled &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;around $7 billion in withdrawals in a single day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; without disruption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“These were real stress tests,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="As-Long-as-the-System-Is-Working-Its-Working"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;‘As Long as the System Is Working, It’s Working’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ recalled that during the height of the withdrawal surge, he remained calm due to confidence in Binance’s reserve model and technical systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“I remember that time very clearly,” he said. “I was still managing Binance. I was having dinner with friends, and they asked why I wasn’t busy.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;His response, he explained, was simple: as long as systems function properly, operations continue normally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“As long as the system is working, it is working,” CZ said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Discontinue ListenKey System in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-21-2026-binance-to-discontinue-listenkey-system-in-february-2026-35363648046306</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will discontinue its listenKey system as part of ongoing efforts to optimize the Spot API. This change is set to take effect on 2026-02-20 at 0&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c90ff3b9f3476410301d3b10d8227a2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, offering an in-depth look into the unique work culture at Binance, a company known for its high-performance and results-driven environment. The article aims to provide potential employees with a realistic perspective on what it means to work at Binance, emphasizing the company's five core values: protecting users, reducing friction, staying fast and autonomous, taking direct feedback, and collaborating globally without unnecessary meetings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The article begins by highlighting the freedom that comes with working at Binance, which operates on a global and remote-first basis. Employees are expected to adapt to different time zones, which can be challenging for those who prefer a structured 9-5 schedule. However, this freedom allows employees to manage their schedules and outputs, creating a work rhythm that suits their personal lives. This autonomy comes with accountability, as employees are trusted to own their time, outcomes, and impact. For those who thrive in a flexible environment and can handle the responsibility that comes with it, Binance offers a unique opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Humility is another core value at Binance, where employees are encouraged to take ownership and make decisions independently. This environment can be intense, as it requires individuals to handle complex tasks, address issues, and remain open to feedback, even when it is direct and unfiltered. The article emphasizes the importance of humility in accepting feedback, learning from mistakes, and improving work quality. This approach fosters a culture of continuous improvement and collaboration, where employees are expected to focus on outcomes rather than personal pride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Collaboration at Binance is characterized by a flat hierarchy, where teams are empowered to make decisions quickly and efficiently. The company values straightforward communication, shared goals, and a bias toward action. Employees are encouraged to document decisions and move work forward in a way that others can build upon, fostering trust and collaboration even in an asynchronous environment. This approach may feel unfamiliar to those accustomed to strict chains of command, but it allows for rapid progress and innovation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The 'Hardcore' value at Binance reflects the fast-paced nature of the cryptocurrency industry, where employees are expected to learn quickly, iterate, and adapt to uncertainty. The article describes how employees are encouraged to tackle high-impact problems, deliver initial solutions, and continuously improve them. This mindset requires resilience, curiosity, and a focus on outcomes, as the ultimate goal is to serve the users effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Finally, the article underscores the importance of being user-focused, as Binance's mission is to create products that are genuinely useful and secure for users. Employees are expected to prioritize user satisfaction, ensuring clarity, removing friction, and maintaining trust. This user-centric approach is the driving force behind Binance's operations, and those who share this commitment will find a fulfilling role within the company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In conclusion, the article makes it clear that Binance is not for everyone. It is a place for individuals who are ready to embrace high standards, take real ownership, and make a tangible impact in the world. Those seeking comfort and predictability may find other environments more suitable, but for builders who thrive on challenge and innovation, Binance offers a unique and rewarding opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Suspend THORChain (RUNE) Network Transactions for Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-21-2026-binance-to-suspend-thorchain-rune-network-transactions-for-upgrade-35366409667298</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will temporarily suspend deposits and withdrawals of tokens on the THORChain (RUNE) network starting approximately on 2026-01-22 at 20:00 (UTC)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">343b7d7045a9d29dd0fee2c89a267ed9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance published an open letter to the crypto community on Binance Blog, and announced that market volatility and pressures have impacted the company alongside the broader industry, reflecting the increasing complexity of the crypto ecosystem and rising demands for governance, risk management, and accountability. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Throughout 2025, Binance focused on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; risk control, compliance cooperation, and ecosystem development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;: assisting users in recovering 38,648 incorrect deposits totaling $48 million, with cumulative recoveries exceeding $1.09 billion;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; helping 5.4 million users identify potential risks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;preventing approximately $6.69 billion in scam-related losses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;; collaborating with global law enforcement agencies to confiscate $131 million in illicit funds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance’s spot listing program covered 21 public blockchains&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, including 13 newly launched chains spanning payment, gaming, social, and other use cases. By the end of 2025, Binance’s proof-of-reserves demonstrated full backing of user assets totaling approximately $162.8 billion across 45 crypto assets. Binance remains committed to responding to market concerns through concrete actions and promoting sustainable industry growth. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance also announced plans to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;convert its $100 million SAFU fund stablecoin reserves into Bitcoin within 30 days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; of the announcement, with a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; rebalancing mechanism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; to maintain the fund’s value above $80 million amid Bitcoin price fluctuations. Binance will continue to uphold transparency, openness, and long-term commitment to advancing the crypto industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha to Launch FIGHT Token on January 22, Airdrop Details Pending</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-20-2026-binance-alpha-to-launch-fight-token-on-january-22-airdrop-details-pending-35333988592242</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/image/pgc/202601/vV2MxKEV9YXtNrJteG684e.jpeg" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Wallet announced that Binance Alpha will be the first platform to launch FIGHT (FIGHT), with trading set to open on January 22.According to the announcement, eligible users will be able to cla&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d31b90350dd972ea9f04a012d5f6d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), Binance founder and former CEO, posted on X stating that this is not the first time—and won’t be the last—that he has faced FUD attacks. He noted that tonight’s AMA will take a deeper look into why and how these attacks occur. CZ added, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;i&gt;"While our (self-perceived) 'competitors' focus on us, we continue to build and grow."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;CZ will host an Binance Square English livestream AMA at 8:00 PM (GMT+4, Dubai time) on January 30, 2026.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="css-jyb3wi" data-area="img"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-imgbox css-nuuble"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="mica-lazy-img css-182lng5" data-src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/9sBULXe2DY4qtTSEjhxTvn.png" src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/9sBULXe2DY4qtTSEjhxTvn.png" style="background-color: transparent;"/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Offers Limited-Time Discount via Binance Pay</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-22-2026-binance-offers-limited-time-discount-via-binance-pay-35404230081417</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, users can start the new year with a special discount when using Binance Pay for purchases. The promotion offers a 6.5% discount on transactions, capped at 2&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4edfc35f5400e3e4108d6f352f482a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that users with at least 220 Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the upcoming ZAMA Pre-TGE Prime Sale event. This opportunity is accessible through the Alpha activity page on the platform. Participants in this event will need to spend 15 Alpha Points to join.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Adjust Interest Rates for XAUUSDT and XAGUSDT Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-22-2026-binance-to-adjust-interest-rates-for-xauusdt-and-xagusdt-contracts-35426249486449</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will implement changes to the interest rates for XAUUSDT and XAGUSDT Perpetual Contracts. Effective from 2026-01-23 08:00 (UTC), the interest r&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24da19e2d2fef7b1b8510d0bc43e34bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that it has introduced new flexible search options to improve token discovery on its platform. This enhancement aims to streamline the process for users seeking specific tokens, making it faster and easier to locate desired digital assets. The update is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to optimize user experience and facilitate efficient navigation within its extensive cryptocurrency offerings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The new search functionality allows users to employ various criteria to pinpoint tokens quickly. By integrating advanced search filters, Binance ensures that users can access relevant information without unnecessary delays. This development is expected to benefit both novice and experienced traders by simplifying the search process and reducing the time spent on locating specific tokens. As the cryptocurrency market continues to expand, such improvements are crucial for maintaining user satisfaction and engagement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance's commitment to enhancing its platform is evident in this latest update, which reflects the company's dedication to providing a seamless trading experience. By focusing on user-friendly features, Binance aims to support its community in navigating the complexities of the digital asset landscape. The introduction of flexible search options is a testament to Binance's proactive approach in addressing user needs and adapting to the evolving demands of the cryptocurrency market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Square Emerges as a Powerful Social Trading Hub, Says Nano Labs CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-24-2026-binance-square-emerges-as-a-powerful-social-trading-hub-says-nano-labs-ceo-35504220149985</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Square is rapidly transforming the social trading landscape, offering a more direct and efficient model for crypto content discovery and trade execution, according to Nano Labs CEO Jack Kong.I&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">244c93c04273cc326eabecdcb93c7951</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that it will expand its asset management capabilities by integrating support for the TON network. This development is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to enhance its platform's functionality and provide users with more options for managing their digital assets. The integration of the TON network is expected to offer users increased flexibility and efficiency in handling their cryptocurrency portfolios.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The TON network, known for its scalability and speed, is anticipated to bring significant benefits to Binance users. By supporting this network, Binance aims to facilitate smoother transactions and improve the overall user experience. This move aligns with Binance's strategy to continuously innovate and adapt to the evolving needs of the cryptocurrency market. Users can look forward to leveraging the TON network's capabilities for more streamlined asset management on the Binance platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Launch New Trading Pairs and Zero Fee Promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-26-2026-binance-to-launch-new-trading-pairs-and-zero-fee-promotions-35594045695874</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to expand its trading options on Binance Spot by introducing new trading pairs. Starting from 2026-01-27 at 08:30 (UTC), users will be a&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">251b8b31fe3e9df06aecfb2fe9afaea3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced on X that users with at least 220 Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the upcoming ZAMA Pre-TGE Prime Sale event. This opportunity is accessible through the Alpha activity page on the platform. Participants in this event will need to spend 15 Alpha Points to join.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Update XAUUSDT Perpetual Contract Price Index</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-26-2026-binance-futures-to-update-xauusdt-perpetual-contract-price-index-35593613649577</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will implement changes to the price index components of the USDⓈ-Margined XAUUSDT Perpetual Contract. This update is scheduled to take effect o&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">550ebc91da956483f9bfc77191f454ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Futures has announced plans to delist several USDⓈ-M perpetual contracts. According to BWEnews, the delisting is scheduled to take place on January 30, 2026. This move is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to optimize its offerings and ensure a streamlined trading experience for its users. Traders are advised to manage their positions accordingly before the delisting date to avoid any potential disruptions. Further details on the specific contracts to be delisted have not been disclosed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Airdrop Opens at 17:00 UTC+8 With 233-Point Claim Threshold</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-27-2026-binance-alpha-airdrop-opens-at-17-00-utc-8-with-233-point-claim-threshold-35642832587434</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced that its Binance Alpha airdrop event will open at 17:00 (UTC+8) today, allowing eligible users to claim token rewards through the Alpha program.According to the announcement, users h&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">296eeea36a8c1d3fd9ef13d3e000804f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;PANews posted on X (formerly Twitter). Binance founder Zhao Changpeng has addressed recent criticisms on social media regarding his 'buy and hold' investment strategy. Zhao noted that there have been&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Adjust Portfolio Margin Collateral Ratios and USD-M Futures Leverage on Jan. 30</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-27-2026-binance-to-adjust-portfolio-margin-collateral-ratios-and-usd-m-futures-leverage-on-jan-30-35642896913521</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced updates to Portfolio Margin (PM), PM Pro collateral ratios, and USDⓈ-M perpetual contract leverage and margin tiers, effective January 30, 2026, as part of its ongoing risk managemen&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e17d0b14a5c3bfd9b3680eac2fbffe95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced updates to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portfolio Margin (PM), PM Pro collateral ratios&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;USDⓈ-M perpetual contract leverage and margin tiers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, effective &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 30, 2026&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, as part of its ongoing risk management adjustments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="Portfolio-Margin-collateral-ratio-update"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Portfolio Margin collateral ratio update&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance will update the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;collateral ratios and tiered collateral ratios&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; for selected assets under Portfolio Margin and PM Pro at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;06:00 UTC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, with the process expected to take approximately 30 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Key changes include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DASH, ICP:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; collateral ratio raised from 25% to 30%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;USDP:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; reduced from 99.9% to 90%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAY:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; reduced from 50% to 40%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multiple altcoins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (including LUNA, SKL, SAGA, ENJ, IMX, PIXEL, RONIN, BLUR, ALT, HFT): adjusted from 35% to 30%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; reduced sharply from 25% to 10%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COTI:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; reduced from 15% to 10%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;These changes will directly impact margin efficiency and liquidation thresholds for Portfolio Margin users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="PM-Pro-tier-adjustments"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;PM Pro tier adjustments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;For &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SAGA, PIXEL, and ALT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, Binance will revise PM Pro tier structures, lowering cap thresholds and adjusting collateral scaling across position sizes. Large-position tiers will see reduced effective collateral ratios, increasing margin sensitivity for high-notional traders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="USD%E2%93%88M-perpetual-contracts-leverage-updates"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;USDⓈ-M perpetual contracts leverage updates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Futures will also update &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;leverage and maintenance margin tiers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; for several USD-M perpetual contracts at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;06:30 UTC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, with updates expected to complete within approximately one hour.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Contracts affected include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;币安人生USDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPACEUSDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IPUSDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COOKIEUSDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RLCUSDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API3USDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YBUSDT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Across multiple contracts, Binance has:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Reduced maximum leverage for smaller position bands&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Lowered notional caps at higher leverage levels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Increased maintenance margin requirements for mid-to-large positions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;These changes are designed to curb excessive leverage and improve platform stability during periods of volatility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Founder Responds to Criticism Over 'Buy and Hold' Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-28-2026-binance-founder-responds-to-criticism-over-buy-and-hold-strategy-35685203836474</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;PANews posted on X (formerly Twitter). Binance founder Zhao Changpeng has addressed recent criticisms on social media regarding his 'buy and hold' investment strategy. Zhao noted that there have been&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37619842f61825f1b206f7e30c6eeaad</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance announced that its &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance Alpha airdrop event&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; will open at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17:00 (UTC+8) today&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, allowing eligible users to claim token rewards through the Alpha program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement, users holding &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;at least 233 Binance Alpha points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; will be eligible to participate. The airdrop will be distributed on a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;first-come, first-served basis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; and will remain available until the reward pool is fully depleted or the event officially concludes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Delist Multiple USDⓈ-M Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-28-2026-binance-futures-to-delist-multiple-usd-m-perpetual-contracts-35688482015002</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Futures has announced plans to delist several USDⓈ-M perpetual contracts. According to BWEnews, the delisting is scheduled to take place on January 30, 2026. This move is part of Binance's ong&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">249becbb23e3fcd1faeaa199ad6f5d43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will implement changes to the price index components of the USDⓈ-Margined XAUUSDT Perpetual Contract. This update is scheduled to take effect on 2026-01-29 at 08:00 (UTC). The adjustments aim to optimize the trading experience for users by refining the composition of the price index.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The revised price index will see changes in the weightage of its components. The PAXGUSDT component from Binance will maintain its weightage at 1%. However, significant adjustments will be made to the other components. The Dxfeed XAU/USD:AFX component will see an increase in its weightage from 9% to 33%. Similarly, the weightage for both MassiveC.XAU/USD and PythXAU will be adjusted from 45% to 33% each. These changes reflect Binance's ongoing efforts to enhance the accuracy and reliability of its price indices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;This update is released under Binance Exchange Rule 17, and users are encouraged to visit the Price Index page for the latest information on price index components. API users can access the updated data through the endpoint: /fapi/v1/constituents. The adjustments are part of Binance's commitment to providing a robust trading environment, ensuring that users have access to precise and up-to-date market data. The announcement underscores Binance's dedication to continuously reviewing and improving its product offerings to meet the needs of its global user base.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Announces ZAMA Pre-TGE Prime Sale for Alpha Points Holders</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/35726957684793</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that users with at least 220 Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the upcoming ZAMA Pre-TGE Prime Sale event. This opportunity is accessible through the Alpha act&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">585e170b52db34c17ccc5c495794725a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to expand its trading options on Binance Spot by introducing new trading pairs. Starting from 2026-01-27 at 08:30 (UTC), users will be able to trade BNB/U, ETH/U, KGST/U, SOL/U, TRX/USD1, and USD1/U pairs. Additionally, Binance will enable Trading Bots services for these pairs at the same time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In a bid to enhance the trading experience, Binance will also introduce zero fee promotions for eligible users on U spot and margin trading pairs. This promotion includes zero maker fees on BNB/U, ETH/U, KGST/U, and SOL/U pairs, effective from 2026-01-27 at 08:30 (UTC) until further notice. Furthermore, zero maker and taker fees will apply to USD1/U pairs during the same period. An exclusive promotion for VIP 2 - 9 users and Spot Liquidity Providers will offer zero maker and taker fees on BNB/U, ETH/U, and SOL/U pairs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;During the validity period, standard taker fees will apply to regular and VIP 1 users for BNB/U, ETH/U, and SOL/U pairs. The trading volume of these pairs will count toward the VIP tier volume calculation for these users. However, the trading volume on USD1/U pairs will be excluded for all eligible users, and BNB/U, ETH/U, and SOL/U pairs will be excluded for VIP 2 - 9 users and Spot Liquidity Providers from the VIP tier volume calculation and all Liquidity Provider programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance emphasizes that standard trading fees will resume after the promotion period ends. Users are advised to refer to the trading fee structure for more details. The trading of new pairs is subject to eligibility based on the user's country or region of residence, with certain regions restricted from participating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Support TON Network for Asset Management</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-29-2026-binance-to-support-ton-network-for-asset-management-35738745123665</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that it will expand its asset management capabilities by integrating support for the TON network. This development is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to enhance its platform's&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55171853f96abfe98467dd37148a745f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Square is rapidly transforming the social trading landscape, offering a more direct and efficient model for crypto content discovery and trade execution, according to Nano Labs CEO Jack Kong.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In a post on X, Kong highlighted the platform’s rapid rise and its growing influence within the Web3 social ecosystem. Unlike traditional social media platforms, Binance Square uses a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;vertical content format tightly integrated with trading features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, allowing users to move seamlessly from market insights to execution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;“This creates a much shorter conversion path,” Kong noted, adding that the model significantly improves engagement efficiency compared with conventional crypto content shared on platforms like X or Telegram.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to Kong, Binance Square benefits from a highly concentrated user base dominated by active traders. This overlap between content consumers and market participants improves targeting accuracy and enhances the effectiveness of trading-related content.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The structure allows insights, analysis, and trend discussions to translate more naturally into on-platform activity, reducing friction between information and action — a longstanding challenge in crypto social media.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Kong suggested this shift could gradually divert attention away from traditional platforms toward &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;specialized, context-driven Web3 social environments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, where content relevance and execution capabilities coexist.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;As competition intensifies across crypto-native social platforms, Binance Square’s model may represent an early blueprint for the future of social trading — one centered on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;precision, utility, and direct market interaction rather than pure reach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Enhances Token Discovery with Flexible Search Options</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-29-2026-binance-enhances-token-discovery-with-flexible-search-options-35738751086649</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that it has introduced new flexible search options to improve token discovery on its platform. This enhancement aims to streamline the process for users seeking specific tokens,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a90450bd2b443455db22a22567c0ce8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will implement changes to the interest rates for XAUUSDT and XAGUSDT Perpetual Contracts. Effective from 2026-01-23 08:00 (UTC), the interest rate component within the funding rate for these contracts will be set to 0%. This adjustment is part of Binance's ongoing efforts to optimize its product offerings and enhance user experience across its services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance users can access the Real-Time Funding Rate page to monitor the latest funding intervals and interest rates. Additionally, API users have the option to query USDⓈ-M futures funding rate information through a newly added endpoint: GET /fapi/v1/fundingInfo. This feature aims to provide users with up-to-date information on funding rates, ensuring transparency and accessibility. The announcement underscores Binance's commitment to maintaining a user-friendly platform by regularly reviewing and updating its services to meet the evolving needs of its global user base.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Announces ZAMA Pre-TGE Prime Sale for Alpha Points Holders</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-29-2026-binance-announces-zama-pre-tge-prime-sale-for-alpha-points-holders-35726957684793</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance announced on X that users with at least 220 Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the upcoming ZAMA Pre-TGE Prime Sale event. This opportunity is accessible through the Alpha act&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcfb6e05d661ea4f6f807e96e745d39d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, users can start the new year with a special discount when using Binance Pay for purchases. The promotion offers a 6.5% discount on transactions, capped at 2 USDT per user, and is available on a first-come, first-served basis. The promotion period runs from 2026-01-22 00:00 (UTC) to 2026-02-22 23:59 (UTC). To qualify, users must spend a minimum of 30 USDT equivalent in a single transaction. The discount applies automatically at checkout for eligible transactions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users can enjoy the discount by shopping through the Binance Marketplace or Hot Deals section in the Binance App. To access these features, users need to log in to the latest version of the Binance App and switch to Pro Mode if they are currently using Lite Mode. Additionally, users can shop at various online or in-store merchants that accept Binance Pay, including Farfetch, Travala, and NordVPN, among others. The discount is applicable only to eligible transactions made during the promotion period and cannot be combined with other offers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance emphasizes that the delivery and fulfillment of goods or services are the responsibility of the merchant, as Binance acts solely as a payment facilitator. The promotion is not available to users residing in certain countries or regions, including the United States, United Kingdom, and Australia, among others. Binance reserves the right to amend, suspend, or terminate the promotion at its discretion. Users are encouraged to update their Binance App to the latest version to participate in the promotion. Additional terms and conditions apply, and users are advised to contact merchants directly for any order-related issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: ‘Not the First, Won’t Be the Last’ — AMA Today on FUD</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-not-the-first-won-t-be-the-last-ama-today-on-fud-35762544054497</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/image/pgc/202601/tdvGNabCqDHdStwB1cY6uG.jpeg" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), Binance founder and former CEO, posted on X stating that this is not the first time—and won’t be the last—that he has faced FUD attacks. He noted that tonight’s AMA will take a de&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf4fc60031baaee10b46286e89c43482</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Wallet announced that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance Alpha will be the first platform to launch FIGHT (FIGHT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, with trading set to open on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 22&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;eligible users will be able to claim a FIGHT airdrop using Binance Alpha Points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; on the Alpha Events page after trading begins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance noted that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;specific eligibility rules, allocation details, and claim conditions will be released separately&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Users are advised to follow &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Binance’s official channels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; for the latest updates regarding the FIGHT token launch and airdrop mechanics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="css-jyb3wi" data-area="img"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-imgbox css-nuuble"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="mica-lazy-img css-182lng5" data-src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/3Dh7Ddp7PNCMLf6momo5Wu.jpeg" src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/static/content/live-admin-api/images/3Dh7Ddp7PNCMLf6momo5Wu.jpeg"/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Reports 2025 Achievements and Plans to Convert $100 Million SAFU Fund to Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-binance-reports-2025-achievements-and-plans-to-convert-100-million-safu-fund-to-bitcoin-35775514215994</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance published an open letter to the crypto community on Binance Blog, and announced that market volatility and pressures have impacted the company alongside the broader industry, reflecting the in&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ddb0e76798a3d3ca78d4f6ed3320423</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will temporarily suspend deposits and withdrawals of tokens on the THORChain (RUNE) network starting approximately on 2026-01-22 at 20:00 (UTC). This suspension is to facilitate a network upgrade aimed at enhancing user experience. The upgrade is scheduled to occur at block height 24,635,898, which is expected to be reached around 2026-01-22 at 21:00 (UTC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The trading of tokens on the THORChain network will remain unaffected during this period. Binance assures users that it will manage all technical requirements related to the upgrade. Once the network is confirmed to be stable post-upgrade, deposits and withdrawals will be reopened. No additional announcements will be made regarding the reopening of these services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Binance's Unique Work Culture and Core Values</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-understanding-binance-s-unique-work-culture-and-core-values-35776678396753</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, offering an in-depth look into the unique work culture at Binance, a company known for its high-performance and results-driven environment. The article aims to pr&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">daf3aaf08c81cd5459b7e939a27511dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will discontinue its listenKey system as part of ongoing efforts to optimize the Spot API. This change is set to take effect on 2026-02-20 at 07:00 (UTC). As a result, several endpoints will no longer be available to users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The affected endpoints include the REST API endpoints POST /api/v3/userDataStream, PUT /api/v3/userDataStream, and DELETE /api/v3/userDataStream. Additionally, the WebSocket API endpoints userDataStream.start, userDataStream.ping, and userDataStream.stop will also be discontinued. Users are advised to consult the Binance API Changelog for further details on these changes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;This update is part of Binance's broader strategy to enhance the efficiency and functionality of its API services. Users should prepare for these changes and adjust their systems accordingly to ensure a smooth transition. The announcement underscores Binance's commitment to maintaining a robust and efficient trading environment for its users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ Recalls $15 Billion Withdrawal Test as Binance Faced Market Panic in 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-recalls-15-billion-withdrawal-test-as-binance-faced-market-panic-in-2022-35789237088482</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;Changpeng Zhao (CZ), founder and former CEO of Binance, outlined how the exchange safeguards user funds during periods of extreme market volatility during a recent AMA session on Binance Square.Respon&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f36eabd1eb4c35ae2bac8b5f0b0d86e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, Binance Futures is set to introduce the AIAUSDT Perpetual Contract on January 20, 2026, at 11:15 (UTC). This new contract will offer up to 20x leverage, aiming to expand trading options and enhance user experience on the platform. The underlying asset for this contract is DeAgentAI (AIA), an AI infrastructure project focused on enabling the creation, deployment, and coordination of autonomous agents in on-chain environments. The settlement asset for this contract is USDT, with a tick size of 0.00001 and a minimum trade amount of 1 AIA. The minimum notional value is set at 5 USDT, and the capped funding rate is +2.00% / -2.00%, with funding fees settled every four hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance has announced that the AIAUSDT Perpetual Contract will be available for Futures Copy Trading within 24 hours of its launch. The platform may adjust the contract specifications based on market risk conditions, including funding fees, tick size, maximum leverage, initial margin, and maintenance margin requirements. The Multi-Assets Mode is supported, allowing users to trade the contract across multiple margin assets, subject to applicable haircuts. For instance, users can use BTC as margin when trading this perpetual contract. It is important to note that futures and spot token listings are not correlated, and a token listed on Binance Futures does not guarantee its listing on Binance Spot. The contract is subject to Binance's Terms of Use and the Binance Futures Service Agreement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ Says User Protection Remains Binance’s Top Priority Despite Market FUD</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-says-user-protection-remains-binance-s-top-priority-despite-market-fud-35788897767138</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;In a recent AMA session on Binance Square, Binance founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ) emphasized that the exchange continues to place user protection at the center of its operations, even amid ongoing market&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23301bf20ccf88a96c018e15c4afe244</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Blog published a new article, revealing insights into the growing threat of account takeover attacks and how Binance is addressing these challenges. Account takeover attacks can lead to altered account settings, lockouts for the rightful owner, and the depletion of account balances. Binance employs an eight-level defense system that progressively tightens security measures as signs of unusual activity become more evident. The article emphasizes the importance of quick action and strong security habits, such as enabling passkeys, taking Binance's warning messages seriously, and securing accounts immediately if anything appears unfamiliar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Account takeovers are a swift method by which users can lose their cryptocurrency holdings. Attackers typically bypass blockchain hacking and instead target victims directly, exploiting their emotions and manipulating them into divulging sensitive information through phishing links, malware, SIM swaps, deepfakes, and fake support chats. This allows attackers to drain victims' accounts of funds. Binance's account protection system is layered and relies on a real-time risk detection engine, ensuring a smooth and secure crypto experience for users across the platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The article details how account takeover attacks are executed, often following a pattern that relies on speed and pressure. Initially, attackers attempt to steal login credentials through phishing, social engineering, or by finding information on the dark web. Once inside, they quickly change passwords and attempt withdrawals before the victim can react. Binance's defense strategy involves progressive levels of control tailored to each specific case, ranging from gentle alerts to aggressive intervention as risk increases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance's multi-channel notifications alert users of suspicious activity through emails and in-app pop-up messages. Users are advised not to dismiss these notifications but to review all account activities, revoking sessions and changing passwords if unfamiliar devices, locations, or login times are detected. For sensitive actions, Binance requires a unique, time-sensitive one-time password (OTP) for verification, adding an extra layer of security even if login details are compromised.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Additional verification checks are triggered for logins or actions from new devices, locations, or unusual IP addresses. Passkey authentication, a FIDO-based login method, uses a device-linked cryptographic key instead of a password, offering strong resistance to phishing and password theft. Facial recognition verification is employed for higher-risk actions, ensuring the user's identity matches the account before proceeding.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In cases of suspected account takeover, Binance can force a hard reset, logging out all active sessions across devices. This allows users to reset passwords and enhance security. Single withdrawal rejection and withdrawal function blocks are employed when risk signals are high, preventing unauthorized account depletion. Binance's risk framework, powered by real-time monitoring and AI-driven anomaly detection, aims to stop potential account takeovers early while maintaining smooth day-to-day activity for genuine users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The article concludes by urging users to remain vigilant, keep credentials safe, and utilize Binance's security features. In case of unusual activity or security alerts, users are advised to act swiftly by changing passwords, enabling passkeys and two-factor authentication, and contacting Binance Support if needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ Emphasizes the Reputation Risks of Engaging in Paid Attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/01-30-2026-cz-emphasizes-the-reputation-risks-of-engaging-in-paid-attacks-35789098214057</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;In a recent AMA session on Binance Square, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the founder and former CEO of Binance, discussed the recent wave of criticism directed at him, attributing much of it to what is known i&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54b44264156d3d0c2ecf19913fe630b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will implement updates to the collateral ratio and Tiered Collateral Ratio for PM Pro concerning specific assets under Portfolio Margin. This update is scheduled to take place on 2026-01-23 at 06:00 (UTC) and is expected to be completed within approximately 30 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Collateral Ratio Adjustments**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The assets under Portfolio Margin will see changes in their collateral ratios. For instance, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/LTC_USDT?contentId=35334156563625" target="_blank"&gt;Litecoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (LTC) will have its collateral ratio adjusted from 90% to 85%, while &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/SHIB_USDT?contentId=35334156563625" target="_blank"&gt;Shiba Inu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (SHIB) will see a reduction from 85% to 80%. Other notable changes include NEAR Protocol (NEAR) from 75% to 70%, Curve DAO Token (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/CRV_USDT?contentId=35334156563625" target="_blank"&gt;CRV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;) from 65% to 50%, and PAX Gold (PAXG) from 60% to 50%. Additionally, Worldcoin (WLD) and Aptos (APT) will both have their collateral ratios reduced from 60% to 40%, among other adjustments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**PM Pro Collateral Ratio Changes**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;For PM Pro, the collateral ratios will also be updated. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/WLD_USDT?contentId=35334156563625" target="_blank"&gt;Worldcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (WLD) and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="richtext-coinpair css-10nd978" data-bn-type="text" href="/en/trade/APT_USDT?contentId=35334156563625" target="_blank"&gt;Aptos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; (APT) will have their rank floor and cap adjusted across various tiers. For example, the rank floor for WLD and APT will change from 70 to 80, with a cap of 800,000 USD at a 100% collateral ratio. The collateral ratio will then decrease to 95% for a cap of 1,200,000 USD, and further adjustments will follow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**User Advisory**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance advises users to closely monitor their Unified Maintenance Margin Ratio (uniMMR) to prevent potential liquidation or losses due to these changes. The collateral ratio adjustments will directly impact the uniMMR, and users are encouraged to stay informed to manage their portfolios effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Discontinue Czech Koruna Services and Delist USDC/CZK Pair</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-to-discontinue-czech-koruna-services-and-delist-usdc-czk-pair-35942410375449</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange will discontinue services related to the Czech Koruna (CZK) as part of its ongoing adjustments to trading offerings. The key change involves th&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b762547aa8e0ff06944c1be3b5b4fb71</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance Alpha will be the first platform to feature &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HeyElsa (ELSA)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alpha trading scheduled to open on January 20, 2026, at 08:00 (UTC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Following the trading launch, eligible users will be able to participate in an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ELSA token airdrop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; through the Binance Alpha Events page.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="css-pr742s" data-bn-type="text" id="ELSA-Airdrop-Rules"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;ELSA Airdrop Rules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eligibility:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; At least &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;235 Binance Alpha Points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Airdrop amount:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;200 ELSA tokens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distribution method:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; First-come, first-served&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dynamic threshold:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; If the reward pool is not fully claimed, the required Alpha Points will &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;decrease by 5 points every 5 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost to claim:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15 Binance Alpha Points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confirmation window:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; Users must confirm their claim within &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;24 hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;, or the reward will be forfeited&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance advised users to follow its official channels for further updates regarding Alpha listings and event details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Delist Multiple Margin Trading Pairs in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-to-delist-multiple-margin-trading-pairs-in-february-2026-35945221810802</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform will delist several margin trading pairs on February 6, 2026, at 06:00 (UTC). The affected pairs include both cross and isolated margin pairs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2a8a4bd932504fc867e04028a93cf39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform is set to expand its trading options by introducing new trading pairs and promotional offers. Binance will open trading for BTC/U and LTC/USD1 trading pairs on 2026-01-20 at 08:00 (UTC). This move aims to enhance the trading experience for users by providing more choices on Binance Spot. Additionally, Binance will enable Trading Bots services for these pairs at the same time, offering Spot Algo Orders for BTC/U and LTC/USD1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;In conjunction with the new trading pairs, Binance will introduce zero fee promotions for eligible users on U spot and margin trading pairs. The zero maker fees will be available to all eligible users starting from 2026-01-20 at 08:00 (UTC) until further notice. VIP 2 - 9 users will benefit from zero trading fees on BTC/U spot and margin trading pairs during the same period. However, standard taker fees will apply to regular and VIP 1 users, and the trading volume of these pairs will count toward their VIP tier volume calculation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;During the validity period, VIP 2 - 9 users and Spot Liquidity Providers will enjoy exclusive zero maker and taker fees for BTC/U spot and margin trading pairs. However, the trading volume on these pairs will be excluded from the VIP tier volume calculation and all Liquidity Provider programs for VIP 2 - 9 users and Spot Liquidity Providers. BNB discounts, referral rebates, and other adjustments will not apply to BTC/U spot trading pairs for these users. Standard trading fees will resume after the validity period ends. Users are advised to refer to the trading fee structure for more details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance reserves the right to disqualify users involved in dishonest behavior, such as wash trading or market manipulation. Trading eligibility is subject to the user's country or region of residence, with restrictions currently in place for several countries, including the United States and its territories. Account verification is required to participate in trading these new pairs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Delist Multiple Tokens Amid Periodic Review</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-02-2026-binance-to-delist-multiple-tokens-amid-periodic-review-35907392575826</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the exchange has decided to delist several tokens following a comprehensive review of its digital assets. The tokens set for delisting include Acala Token (&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5673915da2da5323a6b3bed75e1645b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has implemented a significant reduction in transaction fees for USD withdrawals via SWIFT bank transfer. This change is effective immediately and applies to both retail and corporate users. The withdrawal fee for direct USD transfers through SWIFT has been lowered from $60 to $25 per transaction. This adjustment reflects Binance's ongoing commitment to enhancing user experience and accessibility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Binance has emphasized that USD deposits via SWIFT bank transfer will continue to incur no fees on their platform. However, users should be aware that local banks may still impose their own fees on these transactions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches February Dual Investment Challenge with USDC Rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.binance.com/en/square/post/02-03-2026-binance-launches-february-dual-investment-challenge-with-usdc-rewards-35940567448634</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://public.bnbstatic.com/images/common/feed-og-image-2.png" style="width: 100%;" /&gt;&lt;div&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced the February Monthly Challenge for Dual Investment users, offering rewards of up to 5,888 USDC and an additional 3,000 USDC. The&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">729e4eed06b27fe097178ea30dc2239d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <content:encoded>&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;According to the announcement from Binance, the platform has introduced the "On-Chain Trade &amp;amp; Win Campaign" Season 2, offering participants the chance to compete and win rewards through on-chain trading. The registration period for this event is set from 2026-01-18 06:00 to 2026-02-02 06:00 (UTC), with the competition running from 2026-01-19 06:00 to 2026-02-02 06:00 (UTC).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Trading Features and Participation**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;The Binance Wallet provides both web and mobile versions to facilitate trading. The web version supports fast multi-chain trading on BNB, SOL, and Base, equipped with professional trading tools. The mobile version offers an all-in-one trading experience with features like Pro Mode and limit orders. Service fees are as low as 0% for some pairs. To participate, users must log in to their Binance Wallet, register during the specified period, and start trading to climb the profit and loss (PnL) leaderboard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Reward Structure and Rules**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants will be ranked based on their realized PnL during the competition. The top 200 eligible winners will receive token rewards in BNB. The first place will receive 60 BNB, while the rewards decrease for lower ranks. Participants must use Binance Wallet (Keyless) for on-chain transactions, and only trades on the BNB Smart Chain with specific tokens will be counted. Tokens traded must include USDT, USDC, USD1, U, BNB, or WBNB. Realized PnL from trades between stablecoins or between stablecoins and BNB or WBNB will not be counted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;**Terms and Conditions**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph richtext-paragraph-empty css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="richtext-paragraph css-srnt4i"&gt;&lt;span class="richtext-text css-1iqe90x" data-bn-type="text"&gt;Participants must maintain an active Binance Account and adhere to the campaign rules. Only one account per user is allowed, and any violation may lead to disqualification. Binance reserves the right to amend the terms and conditions at any time. Token rewards will be distributed within 10 business days after the event ends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><dc:creator>Binance Square</dc:creator></item>
  </channel>
</rss>